offleaseonly.com 2019-01-08

# Off Lease Only Inc, Terms and Conditions

  * OFF LEASE ONLY, INC.  
Last Updated: 3-15-2018

#### **OFF LEASE ONLY, INC.**

CONTACT INFORMATION

ATTN: Legal Department  
827 South State Road 7  
North Lauderdale, FL 33068 

## PRIVACY POLICY

**Social Principles**

Our services are not intended for people under 18. Therefore, we do not knowingly collect information from people under 18 without parental consent.   
We share information we collect from or about you in accordance with our Consumer Privacy Notice, if you have a financial product or service with us. 

**Agreements to Privacy Options**

By using a Site or engaging with an Off Lease Only Inc. advertisement or page or account on a third party site, you consent to these Privacy Options, which includes your consent to our use and disclosure of information about you in the manner described in the Privacy Options. 

**Personal Information collected online by Off Lease Only Inc.**

When you visit our Sites, we collect personal information about you, from the information you provide us. The information will vary depend on the Off Lease Only Inc. Site you visit, and may include, but is not limited to: 

  * Name
  * Date of birth
  * Address
  * Phone numbers (including mobile)
  * Email address
  * Account number
  * Social Security number in whole or in part
  * Residential information
  * Employment information
  * Income information

In addition to the information described above, we may collect behavioral information, when you use our online services. When you connect to our online Sites, we may capture the IP address and device information, the type of operating system and browser you use, site you came from, your activity with our online services, and the site you visit next. We or our third-party partners may use cookies, web beacons or other technologies to collect and store information about your visit and use of our online services. When you visit our website or use our online services, we may collect personal information that you voluntarily provide us through forms on our website, or in our mobile applications. Off Lease Only Inc. may also use cookies and other online tracking options like pixel tags and clear GIFs. Cookies are text files that are placed on your computer by the website's server. Cookies enable websites to track browsing activity conducted on your computer. Clear GIFs, pixel tags or web beacons are typically one pixel, transparent images on a webpage or email or other message, used to help recognize users, determine traffic patterns, and measure Site engagement. 

**Our Social Media Pages**

Off Lease Only Inc. has official pages on social media websites such as Facebook®, Google+, Twitter®, Pinterest, LinkedIn, Instagram, and YouTube. When you interact with us on social media websites, we may collect behavioral information such as your likes, interests, feedback and preferences. 

**How information is used**

To enable you to apply for Off Lease Only Inc. services   
To enable you to perform online transactions   
To offer special services and products using advertisements in the form of banner ads, splash ads or location based promotions Verification purposes that will allow access to your accounts and prevent/detect fraud   
For business purposes such as data analysis and optimizing Sites to improve your online experience   
In order to comply with federal, state or local laws   
To share with entities that are within the Off Lease Only Inc. family, and with trusted parties who are contractually obligated to keep such information confidential and only provide services that we have requested them to provide. 

**Disclosure of Information**

We may share information about you with our affiliates and other third parties:   
Third-party service providers   
When laws and regulations permit, with affiliated websites and businesses   
Other companies bringing you co-branded services   
Other third parties, to comply with legal requirements 

**Online Advertising**

Depending on the information, we or our affiliates, service providers and other companies that we work with have about you, you will see advertisements when you are using our online services (including pre-screened offers of credit). Online behavioral advertising (OBA or "interested-based advertising") is practiced by collecting information about how visitors interact with our Sites over time, in order to deliver advertisements that may interest visitors based on their browsing history. 

**Changes to Privacy Options**

Off Lease Only Inc. reserves the right to make changes to this document from time to time. Changes made to this document will become effective when they are posted, unless indicated otherwise. 

## TCPA Disclosure

Off Lease Only Inc. takes your online privacy seriously. We are committed to protect your personal information when visiting and using our website and social media. Off Lease Only Inc. Privacy Options applies to your interaction with Off Lease Only Inc. or any of its subsidiaries (collectively, "Off Lease Only Inc., "we," "us," "our"), at any online or mobile site or application that we own or control ("Site"). According to the U.S. Online & Mobile Privacy Practices Statement, Off Lease Only Inc.'s online and mobile privacy practices are applicable to Off Lease Only Inc. websites, Off Lease Only Inc. mobile sites, and Off Lease Only Inc. branded social media sites or pages, as well as interactions you may have while viewing content provided by Off Lease Only Inc.'s digital advertising campaigns.

© 2018 Off Lease Only, Inc. All Rights Reserved.
